

CONTACT

3

+86 13269607738



toomatapoese@gmail.com



Beijing, China

SKILLS

- Web Design
- · Back-End Coding
- Front-End Coding
- SEO Optimization & Troubleshooting
- Debugging proficiency
- Data Analysis
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

CODING & FRAMEWORKS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript,
 Node.js, Express.js React.js,
 PHP
- Linux
- WordPress, SquareSpace, FinalSite
- NPM, GitHub, Chrome devtool, Google Analytics, Screamingfrog

LANGUAGES

- Samoan
- English
- Chinese

WEB DEVELOPMENT

POESE TOOMATA

A qualified and professional web developer with five years of experience in database administration, UI design, web maintenance, SEO management, front-end and back-end development. Strong interpersonal and communication skills whilst being an approachable and energetic problem solver. Highly motivated working independently, as well as part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

WEBMASTER & WEB DESIGNER

International School of Beijing

2021 - Present

- Build functional, responsive, and easy-to-use microsites for the school
- Test websites across browsers, operating systems, and devices
- Maintain, update, configure, and troubleshoot from the back-end.
- Perform regular website audits and fix technical SEO issues

WEB DEVELOPER & IT SUPPORT

Canadian International School of Beijing

2019 - 2021

- Developing and maintaining a new website (WordPress)
- Administrator for Moodle Learning Management System.
- Supporting all IT services regarding computer software.

AUTOMATION ENGINEER

Symbio

2018 - 2019

- Develop test script, functions and test tools for QA team.
- Master products, understand and analyze test requirement with attention to details.
- Create automation test scripts and execute scripts.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

NORTH CHINA ELECTRIC POWER UNIVERSITY

Master of Computer Application and Technology

2012 - 2016

NORTH CHINA ELECTRIC POWER UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Computer Science and Technology

HOBBIES

- Rugby
- Swimming
- Crossfit
- Golf
- Reading
- Volleyball

REFERENCE

Joanna Cole | International School of Beijing Communications & Marketing Director



Nick Yates | International School of Beijing

Communications Specialist

